In this fast-paced world, often people
are burdened with the many financial and
emotional worries. To top that, they
live a sedentary lifestyle. These
factors make them prone to major medical
events, often termed as critical
illness. Such illnesses and accidents,
can have an adverse impact on one's
finances. An unfortunate death or
disability or even hospitalization due
to such events might affect an
individual's ability to meet his
financial liabilities such as serving a
loan or meeting day-to-day expenses. To
cater to such customer needs, go for
ICICI Lombard's Crit Shield Plus, a plan
that ensures that protection doesn't
stop. It helps you during any major or
minor illnesses or major surgeries
covered under the policy or if you meet
with an accident. ICIC Lombard's Crit
Shield Plus comes with many key benefits
such as coverage for 92 critical
illnesses, coverage for 106 surgical
procedures, cancer restore benefit,
multiple pay for critical illness, 92
major and minor critical illnesses are
covered by this plan. This is a severity
based payout. It covers 100% for major
critical illnesses and 25% for minor
critical illnesses which are classified
into cancer and blood disorders, heart
and blood vessels, major organs, nervous
system, other illnesses. The best part
is there is no waiting period between
claims. And that's not all. Critic sheet
plus also provides optional coverage for
106 surgical procedures. The severity
based payout is 100% for major surgery
and 50% for minor surgery. This plan
also offers cancer restore benefit. So
you will be eligible to claim under this
benefit provided you renew this policy
subject to having received the premium
for the cancer and blood disorders
bucket and cancer restore benefit as per
the original sum insured at the time of
renewal. When illnesses are on the rise,
it's better to stay additionally
protected. The multiple pay for critical
illness option allows you to claim from
major and minor bucket from each of the
five critical illness buckets. In times
like these, don't wait for a
life-threatening or critical illness to
strike and you. Plan for it and
protect yourself and your family today
with ICIC Lombard's Pretty Shield Plus.
Not only are you covered for a major
exgency, but you can also count on quick
and easy in-house claim processing with
24/7 support from our experts.